http://www.picturesalon.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This web site is maintained by Crozier Interactive Partners, LLC, doing business as Picture Salon ("Picture Salon"). At Picture Salon, we recognize the importance of privacy to our visitors. We also recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they provide us, and how we treat that information. So we've developed a formal privacy policy to assure you that we take seriously our responsibility to protect customer information, and to use it only in ways that are consistent with your wishes. We may update the policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally.
You can reach us 24 hours a day, 7 days a week by sending email to info@picturesalon.com. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: Picture Salon, 6225 University Avenue, Madison, WI 53705. We will be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
OUR POLICY
We do not collect personally-identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly at picturesalon.com. If you are just browsing picturesalon.com and learning about our products, we invite you to do so. As a casual, unregistered visitor to our site, we'll recognize your home server (e.g., that your web access is through AOL.com), but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information.
We deliver our printing services through the mail, so if you want to order our products it will be necessary for you to provide personally-identifiable information. This will include your name, address, phone number and, if you place an order online, credit card information. Any information you provide is downloaded off of the web server to a secure system and is maintained there.
OUR CUSTOMER LIST
When you purchase items from our web site, you are automatically added to our customer list. We will not share any of your personal information with any third parties at any time. If you prefer not to receive mailings from us, please advise us by using the mail, phone or e-mail address provided above. Please include your name and address if you are contacting us by mail or e-mail. We will ensure that your name is removed from the list.
CONTACTS FROM US
We read every e-mail that we receive and do our best to respond within 48 hours, if a response is required. We save a very limited number of e-mail messages, but only until the issue is resolved. We do not record email addresses, unless you have voluntarily provided it to us in your online customer service registration.
If you did provide us with your e-mail address, we may notify you from time to time about Picture Salon products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive these e-mail notifications, please follow the "Opt-out" instructions included with the e-mail or contact us at info@picturesalon.com.
COOKIES
Like most companies, we use "cookies" (small pieces of information stored on your computer) on certain parts of our web site. The cookie allows us to manage your session. This is necessary to ensure that we keep your order together while you browse through the catalog and select items for purchase. We do not use the cookie to collect any type of personal information, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer.
SECURITY ONLINE
Most of our forms, especially when ordering a product or using online customer service, use secure pages to insure that the information sent between your computer and our system is secure. This is always true if we are asking you for payment information.
We use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption method on all secure submissions. This method is generally accepted to insure that the transmission of personal information, such as account numbers and credit card information is secure. The most common browsers make it very obvious when information is being passed in a secure manner by showing either a completed key or a closed lock on the screen.
PRIVACY
Picture Salon does not share or resell your personal information such as email address, mailing address, phone number with any third party.
Follow Us On:
Shop with Confidence:
Rolled Canvas (1" border added per side for stapling)
Quantity:
Single Print Price $----
Single Print w 10% disc. $----
Qty Discounts:
Total
$----
Close
